Finding Aid for Middle English Dictionary records, 1925-2008
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Records by Editorial Era
  - Moore-Knott Era 1930-1945
    - Reading Program
      - General Comments, Instructions for Readers, etc. 1932-1934 (Box 5)
      - List of Earliest OED Quotations for Middle English Words, circa 1932 (Box 5)
      - Lists of Books to Be Read, ca. late 1930s-1942 (Box 5)
      - Quotations for A (Box 5)
      - Texts Analyzed
        - Alphabetical, with Comments on Reading 1930s (Box 5)
        - By Series, Journal, etc. 1930s (Box 6)
      - Form Letters and Readers' Replies 1932-1934 (Box 6)
      - Cornell Slips
        - Inventory of Original Donation 1930 (Box 6)
        - Second Donation 1942-1943 (Box 6)
    - Non-MED Materials
      The category non- MED materials at the end of the Moore and Knott eras is particularly full (box 7; 1 linear foot). There is, first of all, the specifically EMED files (reports, budgets, etc.), followed by the extensive correspondence about EMED matters by Hereward T. Price, who was an associate editor of that dictionary (as well as a faculty member in the Department of English) for a long period of time. The files of Moore's correspondence before 1930 and of Knott's research materials on Piers Plowman are also here, along with their individual files on teaching, professional matters, and civic and personal affairs.
      - EMED (Box 7)
        - Reports and Budgets 1929-1938 (Box 7)
        - Miscellaneous 1930s (Box 7)
        - Samples (and a few from other dictionaries) 1930s (Box 7)
        - Correspondence by Hereward T. Price 1926-1949
          - A-Me (Box 7)
          - Morgan, F.C. (of Hereford Public Library) (Box 7)
          - Mou-W (Box 7)
        - Correspondence (chiefly by Fries) with F.J. Sweatman 1936-1937 (Box 7)
      - Moore: Correspondence before MED (1923-1930)
        - A-B (Box 7)
        - C-J (Box 7)
        - K-L (Box 7)
        - M-Y (Box 7)
      - Moore:
        - Notes on Phonetics (Box 7)
        - St. Andrew's Episcopal Church 1938, 2002 (Box 7)
      - Knott:
        - American Dialects 1920s or 1930s (Box 7)
        - Class Materials, etc. 1936-1944 (Box 7)
        - Congregational Church 1937 (Box 7)
        - Miscellaneous (cv's, bills, etc.) 1935-1942 (Box 7)
        - Modern Language Assn. Meeting 1936 (Box 7)
        - Modern Language Assn. Meeting 1937 (Box 7)
        - Piers Plowman A
          - Critical Edition, with Glossary (Box 7)
          - Manuscript Collations 1 (Box 7)
          - Manuscript Collations 2 (Box 7)
          - Manuscript Collations 3 (Box 7)
  - Kurath Era 1945-1961
    - Kurath-Era MED Correspondence, 1945-1961
      Kurath era (1946-1961). Kurath's correspondence has been divided into two parts: the first, in its normal position, is his MED and related correspondence (half of box 8; 0.5 linear foot). Kurath's main correspondents were members of the former MLA Advisory Committee (for example, Baugh, Long, Malone), as well as Allen, the linguist Hermann Flasdieck (Heidelberg), Arthur G. Kennedy (Stanford), Robert J. Menner (Yale), and Randolph Quirk (University College London and the University of Durham), and the correspondence was frequently about details of his editing plan. Kurath was also a prolific writer of recommendations for colleagues and students.
      - A (Box 8)
      - Allen, Hope Emily 1946-1949 (Box 8)
      - Ba (Box 8)
      - Be-Bu (Box 8)
      - C (Box 8)
      - D (Box 8)
      - E (Box 8)
      - F (Box 8)
      - G (Box 8)
      - H (Box 8)
      - I-J (Box 8)
      - K (Box 8)
      - L (Box 8)
      - Long, Percy W. (Secretary, Modern Language Assn. of America) 1946-1948 (Box 8)
      - Ma-Me (Box 8)
      - MED: Kurath correspondence with MED staff, 1949-1952 (Box 8)
      - Mi-Mu (Box 8)
      - N (Box 8)
      - O (Box 8)
      - Oxford University/Clarendon Presses 1950-1953 (Box 8)
      - P (Box 8)
      - Q (Box 8)
      - R (Box 8)
      - Sa-Sm (Box 8)
      - Sn-Su (Box 8)
      - T (Box 8)
      - U (Box 8)
      - University of Michigan Press 1950-1961 (Box 8)
      - V (Box 8)
      - W-Z (Box 8)
    - Administration and History
      - Announcements of Publication of the MED, 1946-1953 (Box 8)
      - Budget and Salaries
        - 1945-1948 (Box 8)
        - 1948-1952 (Box 8)
        - 1952-1961 (Box 8)
      - Committee on Dictionaries Minutes
        - July-December 1945 (Box 8)
        - 1946 (Box 8)
        - 1947-1950 (Box 8)
        - 1951-1954 (Box 8)
        - 1955-1961 (Box 8)
      - English Language Research Center, Proposal for 1951-1954 (Box 8)
      - Financial Support: External 1950-1961 (Box 8)
      - Financial Support: Internal 1946-1953 (Box 8)
      - IBM Typewriters 1950-1959 (Box 8)
      - Inventory of Equipment 1950-1960 (Box 8)
      - Kurath's Notes on Annual Reports circa 1934-1946 (Box 8)
      - Library Business 1946-1958 (Box 8)
      - Monthly Statements of Account 1952-1958 (Box 8)
      - Purchasing Department Requisitions, etc. 1946-1959 (Box 9)
      - Reports: Annual 1946-1961 (Box 9)
      - Reports: Miscellaneous 1946-1961 (Box 9)
      - Responses to Letter of June, 1946 (Box 9)
      - Responses to Reports of December, 1946 (Box 9)
      - Subscribers to MED, 1953, 1960 (Box 9)
    - Bibliography
      The bibliography has its own category (two-thirds of box 9; 0.67 linear foot). When Kurath arrived in 1946, he found the MED bibliographical apparatus quite inadequate, and during the next three years editors Margaret Ogden, Charles Palmer, and Richard McKelvey systematized and regularized the short titles used for citing texts and reviewed the dates of all manuscripts quoted. Whenever the evidence for dating was inconclusive or opinions by paleographers and editors varied or clashed, the keepers of manuscripts in the various repositories were consulted before the final dates were set. Their replies make up a large part of this category.
      - General
        - Guide, Procedures, and General Principles 1950 (Box 9)
        - Stencil Book, with later additions and corrections 1950-1951, 2 volumes (Box 9)
        - Catalogues and Books to Be Ordered 1947-1959 (Box 9)
        - Books to Be Ordered from the Supplement (1920-1945) to A.G. Kennedy's Bibliography of Writings on the English Language from the Beginning of Printing to the End of 1922 1927, 1948 (Box 9)
        - Orders and Subscriptions 1946-1953 (Box 9)
        - Library of Congress 1946-1949 (Box 9)
        - University of Michigan Library 1947-1950 (Box 9)
        - University Microfilms 1947-1951 (Box 9)
        - Jordan's List of Localized Texts (Box 9)
        - Directions for Typing Stencil Cards 1948 (Box 9)
        - MLA Reports on Projects 1939-1951 (Box 9)
        - Dissertations on Middle English 1948 (Box 9)
      - Dating of Manuscripts, 1948-early 1950s
        - A-C (Box 9)
        - Arms-College of Arms (Box 9)
        - Bodleian Library (Box 9)
        - British Museum (Box 9)
        - Cambridge Colleges (Box 9)
        - Cambridge University Library (Box 9)
        - D-G (Box 9)
        - Dublin Trinity College (Box 9)
        - H-L (Box 9)
        - Huntington Library (Box 9)
        - M-Z (Box 9)
        - Oxford Colleges (Box 9)
        - No Reply Received (Box 9)
      - Texts
        - Ancrene Riwle, Dictes Philosophorum (Box 9)
        - Lydgate (Box 9)
        - Northern Homily Cycle (Box 9)
        - Piers Plowman Manuscripts (Box 9)
        - Southern Legendary (Box 9)
        - Wycliffite Bible (Box 9)
    - Editorial Matters
      - Dialects of Middle English (Kurath's Notes), before 1954 (Box 9)
      - Editor's Guide, 1st ed. (with corrections) 1947 (Box 10)
      - Editor's Guide, 2nd ed., 1st typing January 1948 (Box 10)
      - Editor's Guide, 2nd ed., 2nd typing April 1949 (Box 10)
      - Fascicle E-1: Sample Page 1952 (Box 10)
      - Fascicle E-2 1953 (Box 10)
      - MED Record
        - 1946 (Box 10)
        - 1947-1957 (Box 10)
      - Miscellaneous 1943-1952 (Box 10)
      - Plan and Bibliography, 1954 (Box 10)
      - Reviews of MED 1953-1964 (Box 10)
      - Science, Report on (by Katherine Fellows) 1946 (Box 10)
    - Non-MED Materials
      The non- MED materials at the end of the Kurath era comprise the equivalent of a full box (parts of boxes 10 and 11; 1 linear foot). In addition to his appointment as Editor of the MED and Professor of English, Kurath continued during his years at the University of Michigan as Director of the Linguistic Atlas of the United States and Canada, and all of his Atlas materials are in this last category. The first item is his Atlas correspondence, which is mainly with fellow American dialectologists (chiefly Raven I. McDavid, Jr., of the University of Chicago, William Moulton of Cornell and Princeton, and others), but also with the British dialectologist Harold Orton, the Romance dialectologist Sever Pop, the well known H.L. Mencken (author of The American Language), and the Linguistic Society of America (of which Kurath was president in 1941). This correspondence is followed by a number of files on Atlas business matters and on two books by Kurath that grew out of his Atlas work. At the end are some files on his University departmental activities.
      - Kurath, Linguistic Atlas of the United States and Canada Correspondence
        - A (Box 10)
        - B (Box 10)
        - C (Box 10)
        - D (Box 10)
        - E (Box 10)
        - F (Box 10)
        - G (Box 10)
        - H (Box 10)
        - I (Box 10)
        - J (Box 10)
        - K (Box 11)
        - L (Box 11)
        - Linguistic Society of America 1951-1959 (Box 11)
        - M (Box 11)
        - McDavid, Raven 1952-1959 (Box 11)
        - N (Box 11)
        - O (Box 11)
        - P (Box 11)
        - R (Box 11)
        - S (Box 11)
        - T (Box 11)
        - V (Box 11)
        - W (Box 11)
        - Y-Z (Box 11)
      - Linguistic Atlas
        - Account Book 1947-1956 (Box 11)
        - Bank Statements and Deposit Receipts 1955 (Box 11)
        - Bills Paid 1954-1956 (Box 11)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 11)
        - Orders Completed 1950-1955 (Box 11)
        - Orders in Process 1954-1959 (Box 11)
        - Pronunciation of English in the Eastern States, 1958-1959 (Box 11)
        - Word Geography of the Eastern United States: Reviews, 1950s (Box 11)
    - Non- MED Materials
      - University of Michigan Committee on Linguistics
        - Library Business 1947-1951 (Box 11)
        - Minutes and Summer Programs 1949-1953 (Box 11)
      - University of Michigan Kurath
        - Doctoral Committees (alphabetical by candidate) 1952-1959 (Box 11)
        - Miscellaneous (primarily Department of English) 1947-1961 (Box 11)
  - Kuhn-Era (1961-1983) 1961-1983
    - Kuhn-Era Correspondence 1961-1983
      Kuhn era (1961-1983). Kuhn's correspondence is in box 11 (0.5 linear foot). His main correspondents were A.C. Cawley (Leeds), David C. Fowler (Washington), Katharine Garvin Gordon (an independent scholar who was working on an edition of a Middle English translation of Vegetius's De Re Militari), Britton Harwood (Miami of Ohio), Raven McDavid (Chicago), George Pace (Missouri), Robert A. Pratt (Illinois, then Pennsylvania), Roland M. Smith (Illinois), the University of Michigan Press, and Rudolph Willard (Texas; about Old English, Kuhn's primary interest before the MED). Head of production Richard McKelvey and associate editor John Reidy occasionally answered letters. Now that the editing plan for the MED was settled, and the fascicles were appearing on a regular schedule, Kuhn's correspondence frequently involved answering questions from readers and scholars about individual words, usually those not yet published.
      - A (Box 11)
      - B (Box 11)
      - Ca-Cl (Box 11)
      - Co-Cr (Box 11)
      - D (Box 11)
      - E (Box 11)
      - F (Box 11)
      - G (Box 11)
      - H (Box 11)
      - I-J (Box 11)
      - K (Box 11)
      - L (Box 11)
      - Ma-Mc (Box 11)
      - Me-Mu (Box 11)
      - N (Box 11)
      - O (Box 11)
      - Pa (Box 11)
      - Pe-Pu (Box 11)
      - R (Box 11)
      - S-Sh (Box 11)
      - Si (Box 11)
      - Sk-Sw (Box 11)
      - T (Box 11)
      - U-V (Box 11)
      - University of Michigan: Inter-and Intra-Department (Box 11)
      - University of Michigan Press (Box 11)
      - W (Box 11)
      - X-Y-Z (Box 11)
    - Administration and History
      The files for administration and history (boxes 12-13) are particularly full in Kuhn's era, for much MED staff time was spent on three non-editorial activities. (1) Up to 1974 the editorial staff had been quite small, with progress relatively slow, and the University decided that the project should solicit external funding in order to speed up the completion. Between 1974 and 1977 staff were involved in planning for the solicitation, in applying to the Mellon Foundation, and then (upon receiving a large grant) in hiring seven new full-time assistant editors and moving to larger quarters off-campus. (2) Shortly afterwards, in the spring of 1977 the University administration ordered a review of the MED, which occupied much of the remainder of that year, with both internal and external evaluations and a final report, with detailed recommendations. (3) The most urgent of these--the appointment of a co-editor to assist Kuhn with reviewing--led to a search that began in the winter of 1978 and continued for well over three years (into the fall of 1981).
      - Advisory Committee 1978-1980 (Box 12)
      - Budget and Salaries
        - 1961-1966 (Box 12)
        - 1966-1972 (Box 12)
        - 1972-1975 (Box 12)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 12)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 12)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 12)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 12)
        - 1979-1980 (Box 12)
        - 1980-1981 (Box 12)
        - 1981-1982 (Box 12)
      - Committee on Dictionaries 1962-1977 (Box 12)
      - Executive Committee Minutes 1975-1977 (Box 12)
      - Inventories of Furniture and Equipment 1963-1981 (Box 12)
      - Kuhn, Sherman M.: Miscellaneous 1958-1983 (Box 12)
      - MED Council, 1978-1982 (Box 12)
      - MED Library Business, 1975-1980 (Box 12)
      - Mellon Foundation Grant
        - Pre-Planning 1973 (Box 12)
        - Pre-Proposal 1974-1975 (Box 12)
        - Proposal and Award 1975 (Box 12)
        - Planning after Award 1975 (Box 12)
        - Assistant-Editor Hiring 1975-1977 (Box 12)
        - Interview Expenses for Assistant-Editor Hiring 1975 (Box 12)
        - Reports to Mellon 1976-1980 (Box 12)
      - National Endowment for the Humanities Grant
        - Proposal 1979 (Box 12)
        - Award, Reports, etc. 1980-1982 (Box 12)
      - Production Staff Hiring 1975-1982 (Box 12)
      - Reclassification of Senior Research Editors 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - Reports: Annual 1961-1982 (Box 12)
      - Reports: Miscellaneous 1961-1983 (Box 12)
      - Review of Project
        - Self-Evaluation by MED Staff, 1977 (Box 12)
        - Preliminary Report by External Evaluators 1977 (Box 12)
        - Draft Report of Internal Review Committee 1977 (Box 12)
        - Kuhn's Comments on Draft Report 1977 (Box 12)
        - Final Report of Internal Committee 1977 (Box 13)
        - Aftermath and Planning for Future 1977-1979 (Box 13)
      - Search for Co-Editor I
        - General 1978 (Box 13)
        - Correspondence about Possible Candidates 1978 (Box 13)
        - Candidates Asked or Declined to Be Considered 1978 (Box 13)
        - Final Candidates and Comparative Comments 1978 (Box 13)
        - Other Candidates 1978 (Box 13)
        - Negotiations with Ray Page 1978-1981 (Box 13)
      - Search for Co-Editor II
        - General and Candidates 1981 (Box 13)
        - Correspondence about/with Lewis 1981 (Box 13)
      - Sorting Board Construction 1961, 1975 (Box 13)
      - Space and Space Inventory at 555 South Forest 1975-1982 (Box 13)
      - Staff Meetings: Minutes 1976-1982 (Box 13)
      - Subscribers to MED, 1962-1983 (Box 13)
      - Visitors to MED (Box 13)
    - Editorial Matters
      - Articles about MED, 1964, 1982 (Box 13)
      - Editor's Guide, 3rd ed. 1978 (Box 13)
      - Guide for Compositing circa 1961 (Box 13)
      - Kuhn Article "The Making of the MED," 1976, 1982 (Box 13)
      - Notes on Editing and Reviewing Progress 1968-1982 (Box 13)
      - Reviews of MED, circa 1963-1977 (Box 13)
    - Non-MED Materials
      - EMED, 1962-1973, 1985 (Box 13)
      - Page Proofs for C of The Barnhart Dictionary of Etymology (1988), 1980s (Box 13)
  - Lewis Era 1982-2001
    - Lewis-Era Correspondence 1982-2007
      Lewis era (1983-2001). Lewis's correspondence occupies a full box (box 14; 1 linear foot). His main correspondents were Michael Adams (Albright), Larry Benson (Harvard), Christopher Cannon (Cambridge et al.), Margaret Laing (Edinburgh), Hiroyuki Matsumoto (an expert from Japan on the Middle English Destruction of Troy), Angus McIntosh (Edinburgh), the OED (beginning with Robert Burchfield, then Edmund Weiner, Elizabeth Knowles, and John Simpson), Eric Stanley (Oxford), and the University of Michigan Press. Letters were occasionally answered by MED editor Elizabeth S. Girsch. As in Kuhn's era, the correspondence frequently involved answering questions from readers and scholars about individual words, but in addition Lewis often asked for help from specialists on manuscript and textual readings (the responses to these latter letters may usually be found in the relevant word files of the MED proper, which are also housed at the Bentley Library). Part of Lewis's correspondence from the mid- to late 1990s on was electronic, and many of these messages, along with his replies, were printed out and added to the files.
      - Ac-Am (Box 14)
      - Adams, Michael 1989-2003 (Box 14)
      - An-As (Box 14)
      - B (Box 14)
      - C (Box 14)
      - Da-Dic (Box 14)
      - Die-Du (Box 14)
      - E (Box 14)
      - F (Box 14)
      - G (Box 14)
      - Ha-He (Box 14)
      - Hi-Hu (Box 14)
      - I-J (Box 14)
      - K (Box 14)
      - La (Box 14)
      - Le-Ly (Box 14)
      - M (Box 14)
      - McIntosh, Angus 1982-2005 (Box 14)
      - MED
        - In-House Memos 1982-1991 (Box 14)
        - In-House Memos 1992-2001 (Box 14)
      - N (Box 14)
      - O (Box 14)
      - Oxford English Dictionary 1984-2002 (Box 14)
      - P (Box 14)
      - R (Box 14)
      - Sa-Sh (Box 14)
      - Si-Su (Box 14)
      - T (Box 14)
      - U-V (Box 14)
      - University of Michigan Press
        - Fascicle Printing (Box 14)
        - General 1983-1989 (Box 14)
        - General 1990-2007 (Box 14)
      - W (Box 14)
      - Y-Z (Box 14)
    - Administration and History
      - Advisory Committee 1982-2001 (Box 15)
      - Affirmative Action 1982-1994 (Box 15)
      - Authorized Signers for MED Accounts, 1982-1996 (Box 15)
      - Budget and Salaries
        - 1982-1983 (Box 15)
        - 1983-1984 (Box 15)
        - 1984-1985 (Box 15)
        - 1985-1986 (Box 15)
        - 1986-1987 (Box 15)
        - 1987-1988 (Box 15)
        - 1988-1989 (Box 15)
        - 1989-1990 (Box 15)
        - 1990-1991 (Box 15)
        - 1991-1992 (Box 15)
        - 1992-1993 (Box 15)
        - 1993-1994 (Box 15)
        - 1994-1995 (Box 15)
        - 1995-1996 (Box 15)
        - 1996-1997 (Box 15)
        - 1997-1998 (Box 15)
        - 1998-1999 (Box 15)
        - 1999-2000 (Box 15)
        - 2000-2002 (Box 15)
      - Celebration of Completion of MED
        - General 1998-2003 (Box 15)
        - Congratulations from Other Dictionaries 2001 (Box 15)
      - Dispersal of MED Collection and Materials, 2000-2010 (Box 15)
      - Editorial Staff
        - Reduction in Force 1995-1997 (Box 15)
        - Work Changes 1987 (Box 15)
      - Electronic MED (chiefly planning for), 1994-2001, 2007 (Box 15)
      - Equipment Ordering and Disposal 1982-1995 (Box 15)
      - Financial Support from University of Michigan (including Rackham) 1974-2001 (Box 15)
      - Fund-Raising
        - General 1980-1993 (Box 15)
        - Diebold Gifts 1992-2007 (Box 15)
      - Fund-Raising Campaign
        - General 1993-1996 (Box 15)
        - List of Possible Contributors 1993-1995 (Box 15)
        - Contributors 1993-1997 (Box 15)
        - Gifts 1993 (Box 15)
        - Pledges 1993 (Box 15)
        - Gifts 1994 (Box 15)
        - Pledges 1994 (Box 15)
        - Gifts 1995 (Box 15)
      - Grants
        - Mellon Foundation
          - 1982, 1980-1986 (Box 15)
          - 1988, 1987-1998 (Box 15)
          - Financial Information and Reports 1984-1997 (Box 15)
        - National Endowment for the Humanities (Box 16)
          - 1982, 1980-1985 (Box 16)
          - 1985, 1984-1989 (Box 16)
          - 1988, 1987-1992 (Box 16)
          - 1991, 1990-1994 (Box 16)
          - 1994, 1993-1997 (Box 16)
          - Reports 1983-1997 (Box 16)
      - Hiring of Assistant Editors 1982-1991 (Box 16)
      - Hiring of Production Staff 1983-1999 (Box 16)
      - Inventories of MED Documents and Letters, 1980s (Box 16)
      - Lease for 555 South Forest 1975-1997 (Box 16)
      - MED Council, 1982-2002 (Box 16)
      - MED Library, especially the ordering of books for, 1983-1999 (Box 16)
      - Miscellaneous 1982-2002 (Box 16)
      - Move from 4th Floor to 3rd of 555 South Forest 1982 (Box 16)
      - Office of Vice President for Research 1986-1999 (Box 16)
      - Office Procedures 1980s (Box 16)
      - Oxford English Dictionary Memorabilia (Box 16)
      - Plans for Completion
        - Responses to 1992 Memo from Office of Vice President for Research, 1991-1994 (Box 16)
        - Final Editing, Review, and Production 1995-1997 (Box 16)
      - Production Staff: Reclassifications and Restructurings 1983-1994 (Box 16)
      - Reading Program 1982-1983 (Box 16)
      - Reports
        - Annual Reports of Project 1983-2001 (Box 16)
        - Annual Reports to Office of Vice President for Research 1986-2000 (Box 16)
        - Quarterly Progress Reports to Office of Vice President for Research 1996-2001 (Box 16)
      - Retirements and Obituaries
        - General, including Hans Kurath 1983-1992, 2009 (Box 16)
        - Howes, Lidie M. 1991 (includes photographs) (Box 16)
        - Kao, Helen W. 1994 (includes photographs) (Box 16)
        - Kuhn, Sherman M.
          - Retirement and Festschrift 1982-1984 (Box 16)
          - Death and Obituaries 1991 (Box 16)
        - Reidy, John 1987-2000 (includes photographs) (Box 16)
      - Review and Promotion Procedures for Assistant Editors 1986-1994 (Box 16)
      - Seminars and Courses Attended by Staff 1989-1991 (Box 16)
      - Space Analysis, 1983-97 (Box 17)
      - Staff Meetings (chiefly of editors) 1982-1987 (Box 17)
      - Subscribers to the MED, 1993 (Box 17)
      - Training of New Editors 1975-1991 (Box 17)
    - Editorial Matters
      - Articles on MED
        - 1982-1996 (Box 17)
        - On Completion of MED, 2000-2002 (Box 17)
      - Article on the MED and the Dictionary of the Older Scottish Tongue (by Paul Schaffner), 2005 (Box 17)
      - Bibliographer's Notebook: Notes on Additions to Bibliography August 1984-February 2001 (Box 17)
      - Corrections to MED
        - General File circa 1960s-2009 (Box 17)
        - Matsumoto Correspondence 1988-2003 (Box 17)
      - Dialect List
        - Print-out by Library and Manuscript 1992 (Box 17)
        - Print-out by Title 1992 (Box 17)
      - Editing and Reviewing Assignments and Progress 1978-2001 (Box 17)
      - Editor's Guide, revised ed. (with additions) 1988 (Box 17)
      - Fascicle Covers and Publication Dates 1952-2001 (Box 17)
      - Paper on MED by John Reidy (unpublished), 1986 (Box 17)
      - Papers on MED by Lewis (unpublished), 1984-2001 (Box 17)
      - Plan and Bibliography, Supplement I, 1984 (Box 17)
      - Plan and Bibliography, 2nd ed.
        - General and Notes for Preface 2001-2007 (Box 17)
        - Miscellaneous and Notes for Plan, 2001-2006 (Box 17)